{
    "subject": "Ishir\u014d_Honda",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Destroy_All_Monsters",
    "human_readable": "Ishir\u014d Honda directed the film Destroy All Monsters.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.851496696472168,
            "question": "Who directed the film Destroy All Monsters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8393633961677551,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Ishir\u014d Honda that feature monsters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8169826865196228,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Ishir\u014d Honda?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8129259943962097,
            "question": "Ishir\u014d Honda is known for directing what kind of films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7129656672477722,
            "question": "Name a famous film directed by Ishir\u014d Honda."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5897042751312256,
            "question": "What genre is the film Destroy All Monsters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5818397998809814,
            "question": "What year was the film Destroy All Monsters released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5403614044189453,
            "question": "What is the plot of Destroy All Monsters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4310912489891052,
            "question": "Who are some of the characters in Destroy All Monsters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3515785336494446,
            "question": "Ishir\u014d Honda's films have had what kind of impact on popular culture?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ishir\u014d Honda directed the film Destroy All Monsters.",
            "html": "yago_4789_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of the characters in Destroy All Monsters?",
            "html": "yago_4789_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of Destroy All Monsters?",
            "html": "yago_4789_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film Destroy All Monsters released?",
            "html": "yago_4789_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4789_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4789_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4789_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4789_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4789_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4789_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4789_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4789_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4789_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4789_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format with the value as \"yes\" or \"no\":\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention that \"Destroy All Monsters\" is a Toho movie directed by Ishiro Honda, and the text also states that \"Ishir\u014d Honda returned to helm\" as the director of Destroy All Monsters, after Jun Fukuda sat in the director's chair for the prior two movies."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Ishir\u014d Honda directed the film \"Destroy All Monsters.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}